{
    "id": "shokoyamamura",
    "name": "山村祥子",
    "yomi": "Shoko Yamamura",
    "text": [
        "アメリカで現代美術を学ぶ。主に都市の消費者生活に焦点を当て、周囲の環境（もの・こと・ひと）に立ち止まり内省する、敬意や優しさを表すといった自他のコミュニケーションの在り方や他に向かう態度を問いかけ、提案することをテーマとして制作を行っている。",
        "I learned contemporary art in US. I create with my theme that I mainly focus on daily lives of consumers and their surroundings, with questioning to the role of communication of expression of respect and gentleness."
    ],
    "link": [
        {
            "a": "Website",
            "href": "https://shokoyamamura.wixsite.com/home"
        },
        {
            "a": "Instagram",
            "href": "https://www.instagram.com/shokoyamamura_art"
        }
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "Q1",
            "question": "You can recognize musical scale &quot;Ra&quot;",
            "jp": "「ラ」の音がわかる",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "いいえ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q2",
            "question": "You would sing",
            "jp": "歌うなら？",
            "yes": "with someone",
            "left": "誰かと",
            "no": "a solo",
            "right": "ひとりで"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q3",
            "question": "Want to syncronize?",
            "jp": "合わせる？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "いいえ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q4",
            "question": "How much?",
            "jp": "どれくらい？",
            "yes": "pretty much",
            "left": "けっこう",
            "no": "just a little",
            "right": "ちょっと"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q5",
            "question": "With who?",
            "jp": "誰と？",
            "yes": "someone you know",
            "left": "知っている人",
            "no": "someone you don't know",
            "right": "知らない人"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q6",
            "question": "Do you like a sound?",
            "jp": "音は？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "好き",
            "no": "No i don't",
            "right": "嫌い"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q7",
            "question": "A word is",
            "jp": "言葉は",
            "yes": "music",
            "left": "音楽",
            "no": "a symbol",
            "right": "記号"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q8",
            "question": "Do you know a gentle song for the world?",
            "jp": "世界のための優しい音楽を知ってる？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "いいえ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q9",
            "question": "Do you know the taste that feel like a smell of something?",
            "jp": "〇〇の匂いのような味を知ってる？",
            "yes": "Yes",
            "left": "はい",
            "no": "No",
            "right": "いいえ"
        },
        {
            "id": "Q10",
            "question": "Would you like to listen to it?",
            "jp": "聴いてみる？",
            "yes": "yeah",
            "left": "いいよ",
            "no": "well. maybe...",
            "right": "どうだろう"
        }
    ]
}